Let's go.
How are you?
Nice to see you.
I'm your native.
Hey, everybody.
Hey, Baldwin.
How are you?
I'm your native.
Hey, Jan, how are you?
Good seeing everybody. Thank you for being here.
It is 6.30 p.m. Saturday, July 26.
Hey, Samantha, good to see everybody.
Hope you're doing good.
Yeah, we know it's been some...
He's just handling it to easy target Pat.
Right, Mike? That's kind of clever.
Easy target, right? No, that's not just what somebody said. Oh, well people just tick on site. They said beat a thing
She made psyche, but he's just an easy target
Anyway, you're so many semen demons to my location. Well careful, I notice I'm back
Yeah, he's he's like you wake it's tarot
It's that I don't know
Yeah, I was like a little bit just annoyed with something and then like, you know, I express, you know
Just express myself and then I'm wrong for expressing myself. I'm like I'm I'm the wrong one always
Anthony told us to send you doorknocks. Should you just a waste of time you're gonna waste the pizza lady's time
You know this Mexican pizza lady. She might get a free. Uh, he's worked up about you. Oh, why?
I mean, it's like maybe he's like in love with in love either in love with me or be there or something like that
But I don't know I don't I don't spend much time thinking about him
I'm over it
Yeah, I think life is too short to like hate people
Because it's like they don't really feel the hate your only one person that will feel the hate is you because you carry people that carry hate within them they
Sometimes other people feel if there's a kind of rascal action. They're tears of my eyes. I'm okay
It's here's my eyes
Maybe
Hey, low-key
That's just like it sad. I get sad because
It's like I expect people like you know, I know how people are you don't treat me about whatever, right?
Not always well, right?
but
You know, you expect, like, I don't know, I'm not calling anybody out, but you expect
kind of like, you know, your friends to like be there, or at least not to like turn on you.
Whatever y'all don't do wellness checks and shit is a waste of law enforcement resources and dumb internet beef
I know I mean all this happened is I got some pizzas delivered to the house and then or not even delivered because they're not paid for
So I just like yell from the door hello, and they're like oh pizza. I guess it paid for and sometimes I get um, I get the
Like a notification like half hour before it comes like or it's like oh pizza's been ordered on the way and so
Hey evil Ronald McDonald
Yeah, I mean I try to and it's like yeah, and sometimes they go no I might get annoyed and I might say something like
Just out of like being hurt maybe a little bit
Maybe I've hurt people you know without meaning to and I feel sorry if I've done that
it's
The it gets too complicated with other people and it's like I've always told people it's like okay
Well other people see that we're friends and they're gonna try to like
Say, you know, they just get in the middle of it. You can't like take the way other people say seriously, but it's like
Yeah, people are getting the middle of it
Yeah, hopefully that hopefully they do get free food though
I hope that the I hope the pizza ladies get some free food and stuff
I mean, I hope it's not just a waste of time and
It doesn't really like bother me. I mean, it's like what? Okay, my address, you know my address
But if you're gonna do something illegal, then you're gonna be in trouble. Hey black RG. That's a title. Yeah. Hey RG
Yeah, how are you doing? It's just like, you know, those I just based on what somebody said they're like, oh
Like, you know, it's like he's just an easy target
Like I don't know what's up when such an easy target and it's like I'm still here. So obviously like maybe like
The aim has been off or something like that
But maybe I'm just an easy target to them. Okay, good. I'm either
Easy target because I'm gay because I'm nice because I'm you know
Maybe it's a little bit of a people pleaser or and I'll take on
If it's not my fault, I'll apologize to people, you know, even if it's not my fault. I like to keep peace
I don't care about being right. I just care about, you know
Anyway, I'm okay
If it's meant to be, it's meant to be.
I haven't come to terms with whatever it will be, it will be.
So, but I thank you guys for coming here.
Wow, 22 people, thank you so much for being here today.
I backstabbed it, to be honest.
OK, well, tell me how I did that.
You can tell me how, exactly how I backstabbed.
Like backstabbed, what is backstabbing?
Don't cry, victim.
Explain to me what backstabbing is, though.
Backstabbing implies, wow, a horrendous betrayal or, you know, or even to the point of, you know,
just like, it's like one of the worst things, right, stabbing somebody in the back where they can't see, right?
How is that? What did I do? How did I do the backstab? I just want to know what your logic is, because
that makes sense to me.
Oh, are you want to come on? Okay. Yeah, I'm a hairy. Okay, I'm kind of hairy.
I'm not mad at her. She's mad at me. That's the problem. She came at me. I
Was annoyed with like people several times people in her chat. It's like, you know
Saying I'm some kind of like scammer or like, you know, I'm just a bad person and blah blah
Not one word then I then I try to put myself into it
Who are you going after this person for like because the person just said horrible things about me?
We go
Thank you, so I'll be quiet. I know you're fine. Hi
How are you
I'm doing good. Yeah, you know buddy cheers up. Look at me just did this
The cheapest ladies fear I can buy that's what I buy the cheapest lightest piece of shit there
Yeah, and so people like Mike all can just be like when we turn my artificial. I'm listening to you look at these valves look at this
meant
The air I'm so rich my air conditioner. It's like so aggressive
And it's like I got to turn it off to talk to you. It's I'm so fucking
I've seen pieces of shit come up here like oh, I'm so sweaty. I'm so hot
I don't got an air conditioner and I say, you know what?
Take a look at what I got with take a look at that
Apologize I'll fuck a drunk shit. I do apologize. I'm just running my stupid mouth. What up big dog go ahead
You're not saying the truth Mike and you're not a nice person, so you're out
You don't fucking like me. I saw her but I saw you snarl with me the other day you start
Now I'm gonna say you I mean I wouldn't sell
But you know, it's like I'd like to talk to people was like, you know
It's like I don't like to go to somebody's channel and say and they say hi to me
And I say hi to them and then all of a sudden it's like
What up
That's God is God and he is the God. He's the God of my Joe. Did you make psyche?
You wouldn't shave his beard. Is that what happened?
I just said I would have seen that razor should be in the Smithsonian whoever shaved that fucking paste
He did
Yeah
What
Oh, it's too big. Oh, yeah, I need to fix that. I need to fix it. I'll fix it a little bit.
Hey, come on. What is this? What is he, molly holly-o? I don't fucking know.
You're gonna use the mirror, dude.
Yeah, hold on. It's a little bit. It's okay.
Here buzzer. He's taking his balls right now.
He's doing something.
He's not cutting his fucking jugular vein with it. So I think we love you, man
Don't fucking cut your head off with a fucking razor
Let me say one thing. Oh my god, your pants were pulling off buddy
but good times can't even pay for me to watch his chat at least I'm looking at your comments
let me see the side let me say this is here thank you the other side it's being blocked no the
other side those god bless you something yeah yeah yeah that looks even oh yeah that's better
just act like it's still like throwing a virus and put a mask on that fucking ugly face if you don't want
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Like, see, that's because it's a good time to drive.
I'm very shy.
I'm a very shy person, Joe.
You don't know this about me.
I'm very shy.
Well, you know what?
If I ever see you in real life, I'm
going to stick out over you.
My little black dog, Aldi.
I'm going to stick him on you.
Aldi?
I'm going to get his ass, Aldi.
Get this little piece of shit that's
scared of this camera.
I'm not going to do shit.
Aldi's not going to fucking do a damp thing, man.
All the only you don't think only
All the only knocks women out he doesn't fucking knock out dudes. Come on man. You've seen the video. I
Never seen all he knocked the woman out now. You're being down
the video at the beach
Well, no a woman choked him out. He didn't hit her she hit him and she choked it out
He was laying on the beach. Who am I?
I can't breathe, that's Aldi, I got sand in my eyes,
I got sand in my nose, fuck you Aldi.
He started throwing fucking haymakers on these women,
what are you talking about?
Yeah, the thing, the only thing I say,
Aldi is a real man, that guy came up behind Aldi
and got him from the back.
At least if you're gonna fight somebody,
you don't just walk up behind him
and put him in a fucking choke hold.
Aldi was defenseless, that guy tricked him,
he sucker choked him.
If already would have seen that guy coming I'm gonna tell you right now Goddy whatever the fuck your God is Goddy
Whatever the fuck your name is already would have knocked that fuck. Can I say the m word?
Yeah
Say it already wouldn't that nigger out. Hey, he said digger. He said digger. You say I can say it